upost-article.com 2011-05-13

# Upost-Article.com » Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important to upost-article.com. This privacy statement provides information about the personal information that upost-article.com collects, and the ways in which upost-article.com uses that personal information.

**Personal information collection**

upost-article.com may collect and use the following kinds of personal information:

When you visit this web site you may provide us with two types of information: personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected on an individual basis and Web site use information collected on an aggregate basis as you and others browse our Web site.

Personal Information You Choose to Provide

**Registration Information**

When you register for any of our products, services or newsletters you will provide us information about yourself.

**Credit Card Information**

This information is never collected or stored by us. Any information submitted by the buyer will be used only for the purpose of completing the transaction, delivering the product and addressing any customer service issues.

**Email Information**

If you choose to correspond with us through email, we may retain the content of your email messages together with your email address and our responses. We provide the same protections for these electronic communications that we employ in the maintenance of information received by mail and telephone.

**Using personal information**

upost-article.com may use your personal information to:

o [administer this website;]  
o [personalize the website for you;]  
o [enable your access to and use of the website services;]  
o [publish information about you on the website;]  
o [send to you products that you purchase;]  
o [supply to you services that you purchase;]  
o [send you statements and invoices;]  
o [collect payments from you; and]  
o [send you marketing communications.]

Where upost-article.com discloses your personal information to its agents or sub-contractors for these purposes, the agent or sub-contractor in question will be obligated to use that personal information in accordance with the terms of this privacy statement.

In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere above, upost-article.com may disclose your personal information to the extent that it is required to do so by law, in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings, and in order to establish, exercise or defend its legal rights.

**Securing your data**

upost-article.com will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.

upost-article.com will store all the personal information you provide on its secure servers.

[Information relating to electronic transactions entered into via this website will be protected by encryption technology.]

**Cross-border data transfers**

Information that upost-article.com collects may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which upost-article.com operates to enable the use of the information in accordance with this privacy policy.

[In addition, personal information that you submit for publication on the website will be published on the internet and may be available around the world.]

You agree to such cross-border transfers of personal information.

**Updating this statement**

upost-article.com may update this privacy policy by posting a new version on this website.

You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are familiar with any changes.

**Other websites**

This website contains links to other websites.

upost-article.com is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of any third party.

Contact Admin-upost-article.com

**This privacy statement**

This privacy statement is based on a precedent created by

employmentlawcontracts.co.uk and published by freenetlaw.com.
